Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection 1890-1970 AD.MC.002
AbuDhabi
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971 (Box 1-7)
  - A man wearing a tarbouche. 8.0 x 5.7 cm, Undated; Studio Hanein (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A boy sitting on a chair on a terrace with a teddy bear on his lap. 8.8 x 6.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Architecture; Balcony / Terrace; Boys; Buildings; Egypt; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Toys
  - A birds eye view of a group dining outdoors. 8.9 x 6.0 cm, Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Arabic Writing; Drinking; Eating; Egypt; Fountains; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A man sitting behind a desk in an office. 6.8 x 11.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Telephones
  - A man with crossed arms, standing in front of a wall. 10.8 x 6.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
  - A young child walking in a garden. 7.0 x 10.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Boys; Egypt; Fountains; French Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - A man wearing a fedora. 6.1 x 4.7 cm, 1926; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Individual Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A baby boy being a given a bath. 7.4 x 10.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Arabic Writing; Babies; Boys; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A man in a bow tie sitting on a boulder. 6.2 x 5.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Bow Ties; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Two young girls in dresses, standing near a dock. 6.2 x 9.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Docks; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Water
  - Two men and two women, sitting on a sofa. 6.0 x 9.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two women standing with a man, in front of a stone building. 8.5 x 5.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Architecture; Buildings; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A man in a suit sitting by a fountain. 6.7 x 4.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Buildings; Egypt; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
  - A man sitting behind a desk with a scout plaque and sailing knots, adorning the wall. 4.6 x 6.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Boy Scouts; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints
  - A woman with two small children. Same woman from ref1019. 6.3 x 5.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - A group of men and women eating outside (same woman from ref1018). 6.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Drinking; Eating; Egypt; Food; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two men in suits and tarbouches, standing in front of a train. 8.8 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Train Station / Railway Station; Trains
  - A group of men standing in front of an oil rig. 12.9 x 7.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Construction; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Machines; Men; Photographic Prints; Workers
  - A row of houses, beind picket fences. 6.7 x 11.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Architecture; Buildings; Construction; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints
  - A young girl carrying a pot on her head, in front of a small house. 8.7 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Architecture; Buildings; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Houses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress
  - A large family group in an orchard under some trees. 5.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
  - A man in a suit, sitting on a stool indoors. 8.5 x 6.0 cm, Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Two women in hats, with a baby and a man in the background. 8.5 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Babies; Children; Egypt; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Jewellery; Men; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Women
  - Three women wearing hats. 7.4 x 5.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Egypt; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two young boys in coats, standing next to a house (same boy from ref1030). 9.7 x 6.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Boys; Coats; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints
  - A man wearing traditional Upper Egyptian galabeya holding a boy's hand (same boy from ref1029). 9.7 x 7.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Bags; Boys; Cars; Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets; Traditional Dress; Turban
  - A group of men and women sitting on the Ramses II Sphynx in Mempis, Egypt. 8.6 x 11.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Archaeological Sites; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Memphis, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A man posing in a garden in Beni Suef (same man from ref974). 11.1 x 6.5 cm, 17 February 1937; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Beni Suef, Egypt; French Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Kiosk / Kushk; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - A family group in a home setting. 6.5 x 6.5 cm, 23 June 1962; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Arabic Writing; Children; Egypt; Family; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A man in a light colored suit in front of a mirror. 7.0 x 9.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Men; Mirrors; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Two men in uniforms in the desert. 8.5 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Unknown Locations
  - A man in a suit standing front of a classical statue, smoking a pipe. 8.6 x 6.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Statues
  - A woman seated on a couch in a silky dress, another person sits next to her, the photo is torn. 5.9 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Three women with three children on a balcony. 6.0 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Balcony / Terrace; Buildings; Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A woman with four children sitting on the grass. 6.1 x 7.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Arabic Writing; Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A couple standing in front of a car. 4.9 x 6.0 cm, 1 October 1939; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Cars; Countryside / Rural; Couples; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A woman riding a donkey, with a man and a woman standing nearby. 6.3 x 5.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Countryside / Rural; Donkeys; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Umbrellas; Women
  - Two young women (same women from ref1044). 5.7 x 5.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Four women and a child having tea (same women from ref1043). 5.7 x 5.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Drinking; Eating; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Houses; Photographic Prints; Tea; Women
  - A woman holding a baby. 7.1 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Babies; Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Five women posing in the garden. 8.8 x 7.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Egypt; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two women standing in front of the boat the "ΙΩΝΙΑ" with a Greek flag. 8.6 x 6.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Docks; Egypt; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Greek Writing; Photographic Prints; Ships; Steamboats; Women
  - A woman on a wooden porch. 8.9 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Balcony / Terrace; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A woman standing in front of the sea, in a spotted dress. 8.5 x 6.1 cm, UNdated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Beaches; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Seas; Women
  - A family group posing with a motorcycle and sidecar on a street. 6.2 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mosques; Motorcycles; Photographic Prints; Streets; Women
  - Three women and a young boy with a cat. 8.5 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Boys; Cats; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Seas; Women
  - A woman and a young boy standing in front of a tea room storefront. 6.1 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Boys; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Shops; Streets; Women
  - A man sitting on a deckchair on a beach. 11.0 x 6.7 cm, 6 October 1937; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Arabic Writing; Beaches; Boats; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Seas
  - A man in a suit, lying down on the edge of a small garden, in front of a gated property. 8.9 x 6.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Buildings; Egypt; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - A young woman wearing a costume, sitting on a rooftop (same woman from ref1064). 8.9 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Costumes; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Women
  - A woman in a white dress standing in front of a mirrored sideboard. 8.8 x 6.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Individual Portraits; Makeup; Mirrors; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A woman sitting in a leather armchair. 8.8 x 6.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Clocks & Watches; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Shoes
  - Two young women in black bathing on a houseboat. 11.0 x 8.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Docks; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A famiy group standing in front of a topiary pyramid (linked ref1060 and ref1061). 9.1 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Boys; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
  - A family group sitting at a table in front of a large palm tree (linked ref1059 and ref1061). 9.2 x 6.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Egypt; Family Portraits; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parties; Photographic Prints
  - A boy standing in front of a fountain (linked ref1059and ref1060). 9.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Boys; Egypt; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Photographic Prints; Trees
  - A woman and a young boy on a balcony. 8.3 x 5.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Balcony / Terrace; Boys; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women
  - An Egyptian man with a group of Western-looking people in a garden. 6.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Europe; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Women
  - A woman wearing lots of jewelry, posing on a arooftop (same woman from ref1055). 8.9 x 6.0 cm, 17 (?) 1939; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Women
  - A large family group under a wooden trellis. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A man standing in front of a crowd of people with a mosque in the background. 8.9 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Crowds; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Turban
  - A man in white lab coat reading Al Ahram newspaper (linked ref824). 6.6 x 9.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Newspapers; Photographic Prints; Reading
  - A group pose in a garden, one girl wears a girl scouts/guides uniform. 6.6 x 9.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Boy Scouts; Boys; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
  - Four young men in bathing suits at the beach. 8.8 x 6.2 cm, 16 October 1920; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Beaches; Boys; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Greek Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Seas
  - Heavy Machinery Series - A man poking his head through the center of a tyre. 4.6 x 4.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Agricultural machinery; Egypt; Farms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Heavy Machinery Series - A man sitting in the back of a trailer, with oil drums nearby. 4.7 x 4.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Agricultural machinery; Egypt; Farms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Horses; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Heavy Machinery Series - A man sitting on a tractor. 4.7 x 4.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Heavy Machinery Series - A man standing in front of a harvester. 4.5 x 4.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Agricultural machinery; Agriculture; Construction; Egypt; Farms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Heavy Machinery Series - Three men on a steamroller. 4.6 x 4.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Agricultural machinery; Construction; Countryside / Rural; Egypt; Farms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Heavy Machinery Series - A road building scene, with a steam roller in the background. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Agricultural machinery; Construction; Countryside / Rural; Egypt; Farms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Machines; Men; Photographic Prints; Workers
  - Mini Series - Three men in suits standing in front of the locomotive of a steam train (linked ref1077). 8.8 x 6.5 cm, July 1946; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Train Station / Railway Station; Trains
  - Mini Series - Three men standing in front of a large building (linked ref1076). 8.7 x 6.4 cm, July 1946; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Mini Series - A woman with glasses, standing front of a table with a group of men behind her. 8.8 x 6.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Architecture; Buildings; Ceremonies; Egypt; Events / Occasions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Parties; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Mini Series - A man sitting by a fountain, with a young male crossing in front of the camera (same man from ref1080). 8.8 x 6.4 cm, 1946; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Arabic Writing; Boys; Egypt; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Trees
  - Mini Series - A man and two young boys by a fountain (same man from ref1079). 8.8 x 6.4 cm, 1946; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Boys; Egypt; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Trees
  - France Series - Six men having a picnic (same handwriting on reverse as ref1082). 7.2 x 11.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Alcohol; Arabic Writing; Drinking; Eating; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Picnic
  - France Series - Notre Dame Cathedral of Paris, France (same handwriting on reverse as ref1081). 7.2 x 11.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Notre Dame de Paris; Paris, France; Photographic Prints
  - France Series - A man wearing leather gloves, holding a hat. 11.1 x 6.7 cm, 31 May 1927; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Suits
  - France Series - A man wearing a dark coat and bowler hat on a bridge (linked ref1085, ref1086, ref1087 and ref1090). 11.0 x 8.4 cm, 22 [-?-] 1926; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Coats; France; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Rivers
  - France Series - Two men in coats and hats, with the Place de la Concorde and the Luxor obelisk in the background (linked ref1084). 7.7 x 10.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Coats; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Men; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Place de la Concorde, Paris, France
  - France Series - A man in striped jacket, reclining on a lawn with a two story building behind him (same handwriting ref1084 and ref1090). 10.3 x 7.5 cm, 1926; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Arabic Writing; Buildings; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints
  - France Series - A man in a suit standing in front of the Luxor obelisk in the Place de la Concorde, Paris, France same man ref1086). 11.0 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Place de la Concorde, Paris, France
  - France Series - Three men posing at the foot of some stairs. 6.8 x 11.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Egypt; France; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - France Series - A view the Ponte Alexander III in Paris, France. 6.9 x 11.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Architecture; Bridges; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Statues
  - France Series - A soldier standing in front of a building (same handwriting as ref1084 and ref1086). 10.3 x 7.7 cm, March 1926; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Arabic Writing; Buildings; Egypt; France; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
  - France Series - Four men and a woman with a white fur, standing in front of a house (linked ref1088 and ref1095). 11.3 x 6.8 cm, 1928; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Fur Garments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - France Series - A man standing in front of a fountain with some large buildings in the background (same handwriting as ref1091). 6.8 x 11.3 cm, 1929; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Coats; Egypt; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints
  - France Series - Two men in suits sitting in a room with wallpaper. 6.3 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - France Series - Two men in suits sitting in a cafe. Same man from ref1099. 5.2 x 8.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Drinking; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Suits
  - France Series - A man standing in front of the Arc de Triomphe du Carrousel, Paris, France. 8.3 x 11.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Horses; Individual Portraits; Men; Monuments; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Statues
  - France series - A large rotunda with two towers in front of a river with a bridge (same handwriting as ref1081 and ref1082). 11.5 x 7.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Architecture; Bridges; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Unknown Locations
  - Trio Series - A man and two women posing behind a tree. 11.0 x 8.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    France; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
  - Trio Series - Two women reclining on a sofa, smoking cigarettes (linked ref1093 and ref1094). 11.2 x 6.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Cigarettes; France; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Women
  - Trio Series - A man and two women sitting on a low wall in a garden. Same three people from ref1096 and ref1097. 8.0 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    France; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Women
  - Trio Series - A man standing and two women sitting in a garden with potted plants. 8.1 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    France; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Women
  - Trio Series - A man and two women sitting in the grass. 8.0 x 10.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - A woman petting a dog. 6.3 x 6.3 cm, Summer 1961; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Dogs; Egypt; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two couples mounted on bicycles. Names are written in French on the front. 6.0 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Bicycles; Buildings; Couples; Egypt; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two men working with factory machinery. 6.9 x 8.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Factory; Gelatin Silver Prints; Machines; Men; Photographic Prints; Workers
  - A man in suit with trees behind him. 7.3 x 10.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Trees
  - A topless man. 10.5 x 7.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Naked; Photographic Prints
  - Cologne Series - The St. Aposteln Church, Neumarkt, Cologne, Germany. 7.3 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Cologne, Germany; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Streets
  - Cologne Series - A man standing in front of a fountain in Neumarkt, Cologne. 7.2 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Children; Cologne, Germany; English Writing; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Shops
  - Cologne Series - A man standing on the Kaiser Wilhelm (Cologne) Ring in Cologne, Germany. 7.8 x 10.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Buildings; Cologne, Germany; English Writing; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Cologne Series - A man standing on the Kaiser Wilhelm Ring in Cologne, Germany. 7.8 x 10.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Cologne, Germany; English Writing; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Shops